Now that I see that you're
up ahead waiting there?
Hold on for me!
On this long journey that
we've only barely begun!
Friendship, love, courage,
and a little bit of fun!
These are the things.
That even as the years go by!
Will not ever vanish from our minds!
We are all pieces of
a single planet Earth!
Little by little we can
find each other's worth!
And as we see what sort of
form we're meant to take!
All of us know the wind will
always keep on blowing away!
Feel the wind, feel it surround you!
As you finish what you've begun!
Look through that wind to dry!
All the tears as you're bleeding!
The things you must overcome!
Join the quest, join the adventure!
Found in meeting somebody new!
We'll never stop for anything!
Now that I see that you're
up ahead waiting there!
Hold on for me!
All the tears you shed will help
you to become so much stronger!
All the tears you shed
will help you to remember!
Everything, everything, everything!
Now and forever!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, yay!
Feel the wind, feel it surround you!
As you finish what you've begun!
Look to the wind to dry all the tears!
As you're blaving the
things you must overcome!
Join the quest, join the adventure!
Found in meeting somebody new!
We'll never stop for anything!
Now that I see that you're
up ahead waiting there!
Hold on for me!
From what we've gathered, the
following prisoners are assisting!
Straw Hat Luffy in his
infiltration of Impel Down!
Prisoner number E-8200,
Pirate Buggy the Clown!
Prisoner number D-0464, Former
Baroque Works Agent Golden!
A .K .A. Mr.
Prisoner number C-9915 Former Baroque
Works Agent Bentham A .K .A. Mr.
Two Bon Clay
Straw Hat Luffy and Bon Clay are now in
District Inn on level 3 The Blue Goody have
failed in every attempt
to stop them We were
It looks like Straw Hat and Bon
Clay are heading to the staircase
to level four it appears yes
we've lost track of the other two
buggy the clown and Golden report
in if you see either of them
everyone on level two is rioting
and Straw Hat still on the loose
don't know where this is headed
but it sure is fun and here i
thought i was gonna die of boredom
only a matter of time till they
get cut what a shame what's all
that's doing out there well sir
since the blue Kaido can't seem
to beat Straw Hat or Bon Clay,
he took them all up to level two to
try to rake up the prisoner ride.
Why do I only find out about this now
after things have gotten so out of hand?
There was an earlier report, but
you were going Kaku over Hancock.
Accusing me of negligence, are you?
Oh, it seems your guests have departed.
Ah, yes, Mistress Sadie. Salute
the commander. Attention!
The riot is being attended to,
and my team is ready for a hunt.
Hmm, so what do you say?
You're the woman for the job.
Is someone stationed on level three now?
Minotaurus is...
on the prowl.
that's a start but there
are too many places to
hide on level three it
will be difficult to corner
them let's leave the riot to saw death and
handle this on our own
excluding saw deaths i want
all forces in the prison
down on level four now
yes sir of course sir
right away if minotaurus
fails us and they do find
the way down once they
set foot on this floor i
will bury them with my own
hands.
All those who make a mockery of this
institution will suffer for it. How?
It's Minotaurus!
What the heck's a Minotaurus?
a cold-blooded demon
guard a nasty Beast with
the power to toss us out
like yesterday's garbage
those are the eyes of a killer
What, are you okay?
Where did he go?
Strawboy, look out!
Wait just a pointe!
I, I can't breathe.
Second gear.
Go, go!
Jack.
Let's go!
You hang it in there
that looked bad i i think
i almost died i saw the
heavenly garden of oh
come my way you are
certainly strong straw boy
i don't think he's down
for the count but you
gave that be something
to think about oh oh
no no no boo boo boo
you big Moon have you no
shame cosmetics i need
cosmetics stat plus some
point shoes and some
clothes and some weapons and
some drinks some tears and some
oh come my way i think i'll
pass on the tears but i'm gonna
drop if food doesn't happen
soon oh don't worry your pretty
little head straw boy it's
too too easy to get down to
level four from where we are now.
You'll see.
Are you serious?
Yes, but did you get the two-two joke?
I love that one.
Anyway, see that?
Just climb up this wall
all the way to the top.
Just up there? No problem.
Don't just go barging in, though.
You'll need to watch your step.
Right.
What the hell?
My hand feels like it was frying
on a skillet or something.
Frying on a skillet, eh?
You're not too far off.
Is your hand okay?
One, two, jump!
Hey, come here.
Take a look at this.
That is a lot of smoke.
Don't tell me we have to go down there.
It's bad enough up here on the ledge.
Alas, this is the burning heat
hell you so desire to visit.
And double alas, it lives up
to its name quite accurately.
Well, damn.
So what's down there? As I said,
you weren't far off when you
likened it to a hot skillet,
though it's more like a giant iron pot.
Once you go down to level four,
you'll find a boiling pool of
blood and a blazing sea of fire.
We can jump down to the bottom,
but if we land in the wrong spot,
we'll be fried in an instant.
You'll be risking your life
each step you take from now on.
Bon.
You said there was someone
you wanted to see too, right?
So, who's down there that
you'd risk your life for?
I've heard that he's
called the miracle worker.
He's a true hero who deserves to be
free and his Friends call him Eva.
He's the queen of Coverbaker kingdom.
The pink paradise of the Grand Line
He's the leader of the queer folk.
The queen of all queens.
Sounds like a Pretty important guy.
That's awesome.
Uh huh.
I want to see him face to face.
If only for a moment.
But Maybe we can set him free.
Are you crazy?
We just got rid of that thing.
Why did you lead him back to us?
And what are you two doing here?
I thought you said you
were going to break out.
Not you again, damn it.
I knew you'd change your
mind and come with me.
True you.
I hope that thing eats you alive.
We were just trying to hide when
that monster came crashing into us.
Now we can't shake it.
That's where he landed.
Then you're responsible for this.
Of course you are.
I don't want to run anymore.
I should have let myself get
caught so I can lie down.
Damn, stupid monster.
I'm going to run straight to my grave
if I can't get rid of this thing.
If it's come to this,
there's only one thing to do.
Now listen up, Straw Hat.
Do you remember the buggy ball?
The powerful and awesomely flashy weapon?
I used it back when we first
met, blew up half the town,
and scared the living hell
out of you and your friends.
Ah, I see.
Well, the buggy ball is this
big and powerful cannonball.
Well,
I guess you could say it's kind of like my
special weapon, you know, the Pockyball,
named after me.
Well, all right, so nobody
knows anything about it,
but the point is you must have a lot of
confidence in it to put your name on it!
Okay, yes, and it's just as powerful
as ever, only now I've made it tiny!
In fact, I happen to have one with me!
I call it the Muggyball!
Who the heck is Muggy?
Either way, take this, you bastard!
My special weapon, the Muggyball!
Whoa, that's awesome!
Nice shot, huh?
A piece of cake for the muggy ball.
Bring back any memories, Straw Hat?
Won't forget that one.
Yeah.
Holy crap!
What is that thing made of?
Our turn, straw boy.
Hey, three.
Are you sure you can't use
your wax wax power down here?
In this heat, it would
melt in three seconds.
That'll work.
Three seconds is plenty.
Fly! Fly! I'm flying!
Off come my recanpo!
Memoirs of a winter sky!
You ready, straw heads?
Kendall, look!
All right, now go, go!
Now let's ride on!
Yeah, we did it!
We really did it!
We beat the monster counting from hell!
Alright!
Let's keep it up and get
to the bottom of level 4!
Hello? Hello?
This is level 4.
All of our forces are rallied
together under Warden Magellan.
We're ready for anything down here.
Luffy, please.
Stay away!
How much time is left
before they execute Ace?
29 hours It'll all be over by 3 p .m.
tomorrow That's the plan anyway
Not that plans always go
the way they're supposed to.
Portgas DAs is safe for the time being.
We'll transfer him in the morning.
Luffy, I pray that you're
safe more than anything.
That's all I want.
Vice Admiral!
Yes, what now?
We just received a report that Red Hair
had a run-in in the New World. Shanks?
Are you sure about that one?
The timing doesn't make much sense.
Who did they say he was fighting?
Not one of us.
No, Kaido of the Four Emperors.
Did you say Kaido?
That's correct, sir.
Apparently Kaido was after Whitebeard.
I hear it was just a skirmish,
but Shanks intercepted him.
I can't say to what end, though.
Bad tidings, but not unexpected.
These are turbulent waters indeed.
And a brush like this
with the four emperors?
That's a deadly serious
circumstance beyond our control.
With Whitebeard safe,
he'll likely come after us.
I fear it may be Alto war.
No matter who comes out on top, this war
will shape the very course of history.
Set sail for Marineford! Yes, sir.
Alright, I'm gonna ask
you this one more time.
What is it gonna take to make you realize?
It is too damn hot.
Does the boiling cauldron of blood and
fire sound like a good time to you?
What about burning heat,
hell, don't you get?
We are not going down there Aw, why?
It's pretty obvious.
We wanna go up, not down.
Up, up.
Yeah, we're trying to escape!
And that's up, don't you get it?
Man, that is one really big
bloody booger I just picked.
You're not even listening.
Just let him run away, straw boy.
They clearly don't have the
balls to go one step further.
Hey, even my nose is a damn
ball. Your what? Really?
That is weird.
Okay, we are getting off topic here.
How about you stop pulling my tail
and I'll get back to spinning?
We've got some brilliant minds here!
Hey, is it just me, or does it
look like the ceiling's going up?
Ah, yeah, you're right, it is.
There's kind of a loud rumbling,
too, and you know this rushing
sensation, it sort of feels like...
The ceiling's not rising, we're falling!
Oh, no!
Oh, my muggy ball must have been so
powerful it caused the floor to collapse.
You wish!
It was the force of my
heavy kick that did it!
You're both wrong.
It's cause my punch was so
strong it sent out shockwave!
No, no, no.
My wax wax power.
Wait, I guess it didn't
really do that much, actually.
Then shut up!
We're pulling into no fire!
Help us!
Please don't do this, sir.
Please don't kill us.
You deserve whatever happens to you.
That's the way justice works.
How many people have begged
you not to kill them?
It's over.
But we deeply regret what we've done.
Yeah, we're sorry. Honestly?
No, please, no!
It burns!
Keep moving!
Lock that firewood!
It's too hot, my body.
Even my guts are burning.
I'd rather die than put up with this.
I'm running for it!
Get out of my damn way!
I'm through with this!
We've got a prisoner escaping!
Move it!
Or you want to get
thrown into the hellfire?
I'm falling!
What the hell?
You can't just kill other prisoners like
that you want us to execute you right here?
What the hell's going on the entire
upper brass showed up here Magellan
Hannibal and the demon guards I got a
bad feeling something's about to go down!
This is murder.
Fashion your fireproof coat.
Straw Hat Luffy and the others
should be coming out this door.
No update so far.
That's good.
Maybe they already got
beaten by Minotaurus.
A true warden should face
adversity instead of hiding.
Get your ugly mug out here!
Could you ward me first?
It's too bright.
When you inevitably
pass this seat on to me,
I'd appreciate it if you
made it more open first.
Shut up.
This seat was custom-made to my liking,
and I like it closed, private, and dark.
It's a metaphor for how I feel about you.
Aw,
if I'd have known we were just going to be
standing around and
waiting for them this long,
then I would have gone hunting.
Patience, Mistress Sadie, please.
Oh, it doesn't bother me.
But my boys here, they
don't know what patience is.
The only thing they know is bloodlust.
Come on now, come on.
I have an update!
Straw Hat Luffy and the others are now
located inside the Well Tower on Level 3,
which means we're unfortunately
unable to monitor them.
It'd make our lives a
hell of a lot easier if
they simply plummeted to
their deaths from there.
The boiling pool of blood
is right beneath them.
They all have devilful powers, after all.
They'd conveniently sink like stones.
Warden Magellan, another update!
I'm afraid that Straw Hat Luffy
has already reached this level!
He didn't pass us.
How is that possible?
He apparently fell down
here through the well.
But the well leads directly
to the pool of blood.
How the hell are they alive?
From what I gathered,
they used a massive piece of the falling
floor to shield themselves
and lead to safety.
The bastards have luck on
their side. One more thing.
What now?
It stinks, Warden.
I mean this situation.
It stinks.
Well, sir,
the demon guard Minotaurus also fell into
the well, and apparently he's not moving.
Impossible.
They defeated him.
It appears so.
The poor baby.
I won't believe it!
Pull it together!
You will follow my orders carefully.
There are only two ways to get out
of level 4 that don't include dying.
We have two staircases they can take that
aren't currently protected
by security guards.
From this point forward, we're
splitting our forces into three.
Hannibal, I want you in
charge of this stairwell.
Block all access to level 3.
Mistress Sadie,
I want you and the Demon Guards to defend
the stairwell leading to level five.
No way!
That sounds so boring.
I want to punish those bad boys.
Surely my outfit makes
that clear enough to you.
Maybe I'll just let them slip past me
and have the Warden take the blame.
Any objections?
Please, Warden, don't do that.
But I didn't complain this
time. You don't need to.
I can sense you plotting against me.
Oh, and once they're captured, you're
free to do as you wish with them.
Oh, yes, sir.
I can get behind that idea.
And as for the rest of the guards, I
want you to pursue them at all costs.
You bring them to me dead or alive. Sir!
Almost dead works too.
This ends right now.
They have toyed with me long enough.
We have a reputation to uphold.
The burning heat hell
shall be their last stop.
The floor is insanely hot in here.
It's so hot my lungs feel
like they're full of fire.
Now should we move the faster
we get out of this place?
Now which way should we go?
You guys sound like babies.
Why me babies?
It's mind over matter.
Just pretend the fire's your friend.
Honestly, I can't really
blame you, though.
I do admit it's a little steamy in
here, even compared to that desert.
Actually, maybe more than just a little...
My friend, the fire
might be turning on me.
Oh, crap!
Your blathering is worse
than the damn heat!
I know which way!
Follow me!
Where are you going?
So hot!
We're aware of that huh?
Now where could our little
straw boy be leading us?
Of course to the kitchen.
Good because I'm famished.
Wait for me, old chum!
I'm not gonna lie food does sound good.
Kind of hoping for some booze.
No.
Wait a Spitted buggy!
That food smells so good!
Hot, hot, hot, hot!
Oh, boy, I can't wait for Yanni food.
There he is!
It's a Straw Hat oofy!
Tang, there's a bunch of them!
Oh, this heat's beating me down!
But I'll get my energy back
once I get some food in me!
Stop right there!
Gum-Gum!
Fireworks!
What are you freaking out about, partner?
Open your eyes and take a look!
There's an ocean of guards down there.
And think,
this level is devoted to
the agony of the prisoners,
yet there's not a single guard
manning the fire torture pit.
Let's go get a move on the first thing we
should do is to check
the staircases i've got
a feeling They ambushed us with all these
guards they probably
boxed us in on this level
What if they've been waiting
on level four this whole
time that means they just
want Straw Hat We weren't even
trying to come down here
maybe not but we are still
trying to break out and they
do know our names and faces.
Still, there's something
even more troubling.
If they're sending this
many guards after us,
it's extremely likely they're
also sending in the Impel?
down All-Stars to put
an end to this chaos.
And I'm not just talking about the
other three demon guards, either.
Warden Magellan himself might make an
appearance, and then we're dead, my friend.
Quit blocking the phone!
Whoa!
Freak me out!
I thought it was a spear
or something heading at me.
What is that?
Aw, jeez! Gross!
Oh, no, no!
It's time to put an end to your
buffoonery once and for all, boy.
Who are you?
It's Magellan!
I've got you now, you criminal scum!